The solution is right under our feet.
Kiss the Ground is a documentary film directed by Rebecca Harrell Tickell.
Sheds light on an alternative approach to farming called “regenerative agriculture” that could
balance our climate, replenish our vast water supplies, and feed the world.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Woody Harrelson.
Self, played by David Arquette.
Self, played by Gisele Bündchen.
Self, played by Rosario Dawson.
Self, played by Jason Mraz.
Self, played by Ian Somerhalder.
Kiss the Ground is a 2020 Netflix original documentary
film streaming on Amazon Prime Video.
It focuses on regenerative agriculture; the movie profiles scientists, farmers and environmentalists as
they explore the important role healthier soil plays in better human and planetary health.
The film is narrated by actor Woody Harrelson and contains a celebrity
cast that includes Gisele Bündchen, Tom Brady, and others.
Directed by Josh Tickell and Rebecca Harrell Tickell, the films are the result of a partnership between Kiss the Ground—a 501(c)(3) nonprofit
organization headquartered in Los Angeles—and Big Picture Ranch, a film production company based in Ojai, California, northwest of L.A.
The film explores themes of climate, climate change,
earth, agriculture, water supply.